https://tripleaughtdesign.com/privacy/

Support
2020 Holiday Season Shipping Updates HERE.
Privacy Policy
Triple Aught Design is committed to respecting the privacy rights of all visitors to our website. The following policy describes how Triple Aught Design collections protects and uses information we receive from visitors to our web site.
What information does Triple Aught Design collection and how do we use it?
When ordering products on our web site, we need you to provide your name, email address, billing and mailing addresses, phone number and credit card information. This information is required for us to process customer transactions. Providing a password allows us to provide a faster method for you to place subsequent orders.
If you choose to join Triple Aught Design's mailing list, we will collect your email address, name and gender, and use these details to provide marketing or promotional content. You may opt out of our mailing list at any time by selecting the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any newsletter, or by contact our Customer Support team. Registering for an account on our web site does not automatically subscribe you to our mailing list.
When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, Triple Aught Design may again ask for your name, address, email address, username and password so that we are able to better administer the contest and notify winners.
We may also use the information we collect during the registration process to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the web site or new Triple Aught Design services.
California Privacy Rights (California Civil Code Section 1798.83)
A California resident who has provided personal information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household purposes ("California customer") is entitled to request information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of personal information, upon receipt of a request by a California customer, the business is required to provide a list of all third parties to whom personal information was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of personal information that were disclosed.
However, under law, a business is not required to provide the above-described lists if the business adopts and discloses to the public (in its privacy policy) a policy of not disclosing customer's personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless the customer first affirmatively agrees to the disclosure, as long as the business maintains and discloses this policy. Rather, the business may comply with the law by notifying the customer of his or her right to prevent disclosure of personal information and providing a cost free means to exercise that right.
As stated in our Privacy Policy, we do not share information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless you affirmatively agree to such disclosure, typically by opting in to receive information from a third party. If you do ask us to share your information with a third party for its marketing purposes, we will only share information in connection with that specific promotion, as we do not share information with any third party on a continual basis. To prevent disclosure of your personal information for use in direct marketing by a third party, do not opt in to such use when you provide personally identifiable information on one of our sites. Please note that whenever you opt in to receive future communications from a third party, your information will be subject to the third party's privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact the third party directly, as we have no control over how third parties use information. You should always review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information.
California customers may request further information about our compliance with this law by contacting Customer Support. Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this email address.
How does Triple Aught Design protect visitor information?
All sensitive/credit information supplied by users is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
Does Triple Aught Design use "cookies"?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experience and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help Triple Aught Design conduct and improve its business. Google Analytics is a third-party service provider that Triple Aught Design works with to help analyze and improve how visitors interact with our website and services. They use cookies to gather anonymous data about our visitors on Triple Aught Design's behalf. They do not collect personally identifiable information like email, credit card number, phone number, or name.
Does Triple Aught Design disclose the information we collect from our visitors to outside parties?
Triple Aught Design does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting Triple Aught Design's business, or servicing you as long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or other rights or safety. This information is also used to better understand visitor's use of Triple Aught Design's website and to support related transactions made on the website.
However, this data in aggregate form may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Triple Aught Design may also use email addresses and other personally identifiable information to contact visitors who communicate with us. For example, we direct email to visitors who provide us with their email addresses for specific purposes such as receiving our email newsletters or being notified if they have won one of our contests. Each email newsletter always contains instructions on how to discontinue receipt of the newsletter. However, if a visitor at anytime chooses to no longer receive such information and opt-out from any future mailings, they should simple click unsubscribe link on any Triple Aught Design email sent to them and follow the instructions provided.
Third party links
In an attempt to provide increased value to our visitors, Triple Aught Design may choose various third party websites to link to from our own website. However, Triple Aught Design has no control over these linked websites which each have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of Triple Aught Design. Triple Aught Design has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. These linked websites are only for your convenience and you therefore access them at your own risk. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our website and the links placed upon it and therefore we request feedback on not only our own website, but for websites we link to as well (including if a specific link does not work).
Your consent
By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Triple Aught Design. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Feedback
Triple Aught Design welcomes your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to this or any other issue.
Legal
Please also visit Triple Aught Design's terms and conditions establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of the entire Triple Aught Design website.
Your Right to Data
You may contact us using the details below to request access to the personal data that is processed about you, to have erroneous personal data corrected, to request that we erase your personal data, to request that the processing of your personal data is restricted, to exercise your right to data portability, to withdraw consent to particular processing (where such consent has been obtained) and to object to the processing of your personal data.
Contact information
This website is operated by:
Triple Aught Design, LLC 660 22nd Street San Francisco, CA 94107
1-866-613-1386
support@tripleaughtdesign.com
Changes to our policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.
Last modified: 2018-05-24T16:10:33.667592-07:00
